Guide to the Family Life Development Center records, 1974-2010.
Family Life Development Center records, 1974-2010
- Series II: Curriculum
  - B. Child Protective Services Training, Institute (1973-2001)
    - ---. Part II: Assertive Supervision and Negotiation Skills. Draft. (Box 13, Folder 12-14)
    - Part III: Conflict Negotiation and Motivation. Draft. (Box 13, Folder 15-17)
    - Griffin, William, et al. Investigation Issues. Guidebook for NYS Child Protective Service Staff., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Harrigan, C. Frank, et al. Legal Issues in Child Protective Services. Advanced course guidebook for NYS Child Protective Service workers., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - McCabe, Mary Ann. Sexual Abuse. CPSTI. (2 parts)., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 20-21)
    - Monroe County Department of Social Services. Staff Development Service Training. (6 parts), 1989 (Box 13, Folder 22-27)
    - Rycus, Judith and Ronald C. Hughes. Casework Process and Case Planning in Child Protective Services. A training curriculum., Target: Competent Staff. Competency-based inservice training for Child Welfare.; 1989 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Rycus, Judith, et al. Child Protective Services. A training curriculum. (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - ---. Separation and Placement in Child Protective Services. A Training curriculum. (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Tooman, Patrick. The Sexual Abuse Interview Guidebook., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - ---. Sexual Abuse issues., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Wells, Barbara. High Risk Families. Advanced course guidebook for NYS Child Protective Service workers., 1989 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Abramczyk, Lois, et al. Caseworker Competency-Based Curriculum Child Abuse and Neglect Workbook. Louisiana Department of Social Services, Office of Community Services., 1990 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Beeler, Nan Giblin, et al. The Effects of Abuse and Neglect on Child Development. A training curriculum., 1990 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - CPSTI. Management De-Briefing; Institutional Abuse Training; Building a Theory of a Case. New York State Department of Social Services, Division of Family and Children's Services. ( 2 parts), 1990 (Box 14, Folder 3-4)
    - ---. IAB Management Seminar Series. Guidebook for NYS Child Protective Service workers., 1990 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - ---. New York State Risk Assessment and Services Planning Model. Training guidebook. (3 parts), 1990 (Box 14, Folder 6-8)
    - ---. New York State Risk Assessment Training Guidebook., 1990 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - FLDC Projects, Rural Services Training Project: seminars, quarter reports; NCCAN research grant status report;; Quarterly performance report, The Academic Effects of Child Abuse and Neglect;; Monthly report narrative, Children's Justice and Assistance Act. Rosaleen Mazur, project director;; Training Institute on Child Sexual Abuse, conducted at Kings County Hospital and Jacobi Hospital;; Eckenrode, John and Molly Laird. The Impact of Child Maltreatment on Academic Performance.; 1990 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - National Data Archive on Child Abuse and Neglect, "Updata"; Concept paper, "School District 10/Cornell Model for Parent-School Involvement"; National Residential Child Care Project. Training of Trainers in Therapeutic Crisis Intervention; New York State DSS Statewide Training Calendar, July 1-Sep. 30, 1992; Doris, John. NCCAN Prevention of Physical Child Abuse and Neglect. Project request forms, approval forms, correspondence, grants., 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Budjet projections 1991-1994; Doris, John and Frank Barry. NCCAN Prevention of Physical Child Abuse and Neglect.; CC6 Train-the-Trainer for New York City Day Care Programs.; Curriculum Vitae. (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Johnson, John and Frank Bary. Rural Case Management. Rural Services Training Project. Participant Manual., 1990 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - McPheron, Mary Lu and Brenda Solomon. Child Protective Services Interviewing. Participant's workbook., 1992 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - New York State Department of Social Services. New York State Risk Assessment and Services Planning Manual. (2 parts), 1992 (Box 14, Folder 15-16)
    - Nunno, Michael. A Guide to New York State's Child Protective Services Law, Title 6, Article 6: Social Services Law. Slide set script., 1991 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Rab, Joel and Joan Van Hull. Delivery of Child Welfare SErvices to High-Risk Families. Trainer's manual: Volume I. (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - The Suggestibility of Children's Recollections. Ed. John Doris. (2 parts), 1991 (Box 14, Folder 19-20)
    - ---. Various notes. (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - ---. Draft. (2 parts) (Box 14, Folder 22-23)
  - Child Protective Services Worker Training Institute (CPSTI) (Box 15)
  - Training Guidebooks and Trainer Manuals, 1980-2001 (Box 15)
  - Administering C.P.S. Guidebook, 1984-06 (Box 15)
  - Administering C.P.S. Trainers Manual, 1985-02 (Box 15)
  - Adolescent Maltreatment Guidebook, 1989-03 (Box 15)
  - Adolescent Maltreatment Trainers Manual, 1989-03 (Box 15)
  - APSAC Guidelines for Adolescents, 1995 (Box 15)
  - HDS CAN Adolescent Abuse and Neglect, 1980-07 (Box 15)
  - Assessment In C. P. S. Guidebook, 1981 (Box 15)
  - Assessment In C. P. S. Trainer Manual, 1981 (Box 15)
  - Children At Risk Guidebook, 1988-10 (Box 15)
  - Children At Risk Guidebook, 1989-05 (Box 15)
  - CPS Interviewing Workbook, 1992 (Box 15)
  - CPS Issues For Non CPS Staff Guidebook, 1986-05 (Box 15)
  - CPS Issues For Non CPS Staff Trainer Manual, 1986-05 (Box 15)
  - Cultural Issues in C.P.S. Guidebook, 1983-1984 (Box 15)
  - Domestic Violence: Battered Women and Their Children Guidebook Vol. I, 1986-03 (Box 15)
  - Domestic Violence: Battered Women and Their Children Guidebook Vol. II, 1986-03 (Box 15)
  - Domestic Violence: Battered Women and Their Children Guidebook, 1987-03 (Box 15)
  - Families and Substance Abuse Guidebook, 1990-02-06 (Box 15)
  - High Risk Parenting Guidebook, 1984-01 (Box 15)
  - High Risk Parenting Trainers Manual, 1984-05 (Box 15)
  - High Risk Parenting Guidebook, 1985-12 (Box 15)
  - High Risk Parenting Trainers Manual, 1985-12 (Box 15)
  - High Risk Families Guidebook, 1989-01 (Box 15)
  - High Risk Families Guidebook, 1989-08 (Box 15)
  - High Risk Families Guidebook, 1993 (Box 15)
  - High Risk Factors (Box 15)
  - For Children Under Six Guidebook, 1982 (Box 15)
  - High Risk Factors (Box 15)
  - For Children Under Six Guidebook, 1983-1984 (Box 15)
  - Intra-Familial Sexual Abuse (Box 15)
  - Dynamics and Intervention Guidebook (Box 15)
  - Edition Three, 1995 (Box 15)
  - Intra-Familial Sexual Abuse (Box 15)
  - Dynamics and Intervention Trainer Manual (Box 15)
  - Edition Three, 1995 (Box 15)
  - Investigation and Assessment Workbook, 1991-10-06 (Box 15)
  - Adv. Investigation Training Issues Guidebook, 1982-1983 (Box 15)
  - Adv. Investigation Training Issues Trainers Manual, 1982-1983 (Box 15)
  - Investigative Issues Guidebook, 1986-03 (Box 15)
  - Investigation Training Issues Guidebook, 1989-01 (Box 15)
  - Investigation Training Issues Trainers Manual, 1989-01 (Box 15)
  - Investigation Skills and Techniques Guidebook, 1992 (Box 15)
  - Investigation Skills and Techniques Trainers Manual, 1992 (Box 15)
  - Legal Desk Reference Manual, 1983-11 (Box 16)
  - Legal Desk Reference Trainers Manual, 1983-01 (Box 16)
  - Legal Desk Reference Workbook, 1984-1985 (Box 16)
  - Supplement to Legal Desk Reference, 1986-06 (Box 16)
  - Legal Issues in CPS Trainers Manual, 1986 (Box 16)
  - Legal Issues in CPS Trainers Manual, 1995 (Box 16)
  - Medical Issues In CPS Guidebook, 1982-08 (Box 16)
  - Medical Issues In CPS Guidebook, 1982 (Box 16)
  - Medical Issues In CPS Trainers Manual, 1982 (Box 16)
  - Medical Issues In CPS Guidebook, 1983 (Box 16)
  - Medical Issues In CPS Guidebook, 1984-1985 (Box 16)
  - Medical Issues In CPS Guidebook, 1986-03 (Box 16)
  - Medical Issues In CPS Guidebook, 1987-06 (Box 16)
  - Medical Issues In CPS Guidebook, 1988-09 (Box 16)
  - Medical Issues In CPS Guidebook, 1993 (Box 16)
  - Medical Issues In CPS Guidebook, 1995 (Box 16)
  - On Call Trainers Manual, 1984-01 (Box 16)
  - On Call Trainers Manual, 1984-07 (Box 16)
  - On Call Guidebook, 1985-10 (Box 16)
  - On Call Guidebook, 1995 (Box 16)
  - On Call Trainers Manual, 1996 (Box 16)
  - Sexual Abuse Trainers Manual, 1983 (Box 16)
  - Sexual Abuse Trainers Manual, 1984-1985 (Box 16)
  - Sexual Abuse Guidebook, 1986-07 (Box 16)
  - Sexual Abuse Guidebook, 1987-10 (Box 16)
  - Sexual Abuse Guidebook, 1987 (Box 16)
  - Sexual Abuse Guidebook, 1989-04 (Box 16)
  - Sexual Abuse Guidebook, 1989 (Box 16)
  - Sexual Abuse Interview Guidebook, 1989-01 (Box 16)
  - Sexual Abuse Interview Guidebook, 1994 (Box 16)
  - Sexual Abuse Interview Workbook, 1997 (Box 16)
  - Sexual Abuse Interview Pre-Reading, 1997 (Box 16)
  - Sexual Abuse Interview Trainers Manual, 1997 (Box 16)
  - Sexual Abuse Dynamics and Intervention Guidebook Edition Two, 1995 (Box 17)
  - Sexual Abuse Dynamics and Intervention Guidebook Edition Three, 1995 (Box 17)
  - CORE Training for Child Protective Supervisors, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Guidebook For New York State Child Protective Services Staff, 1984-10 (Box 17)
  - CORE Training for Child Protective Supervisors Vol. I, 1984-01 (Box 17)
  - Guidebook For New York State Child Protective Services Staff Vol. II, 1984-01 (Box 17)
  - Participant Guidebook Administering CPS, 1985-03 (Box 17)
  - Guidebook for New York State Child Protective Services Staff Vol. I, 1985-10 (Box 17)
  - CORE Training for Child Protective Supervisors Vol. II, 1986-06 (Box 17)
  - Trainer Manual for New York State Child Protective Services Staff Vol. Two, 1988-04 (Box 17)
  - Trainers Manual for Core Training Week I and II, 1989-02 (Box 17)
  - CORE Guidebook for the New York State Child Protective Services Staff Vol. I, 1989 (Box 17)
  - CORE Guidebook for the New York State Child Protective Services Staff Vol. II, 1989 (Box 17)
  - CORE Guidebook for the New York State Child Protective Services Staff Vol. I Edition Two, 1990 (Box 17)
  - CORE Guidebook for the New York State Child Protective Services Staff Vol. II Edition Two, 1990 (Box 17)
  - CORE Guidebook for the New York State Child Protective Services Staff Vol. I Edition Three, 1992 (Box 17)
  - CORE Guidebook for the New York State Child Protective Services Staff Vol. II Edition Three, 1992 (Box 17)
  - Supervisory Guidebook to New York State Child Protective Services Core Training, 1992 (Box 17)
  - Core Training For New York State Child Protective Services Workers Trainers Manual Edition Two, 1994 (Box 17)
  - Core Training For New York State Child Protective Services Workers Trainers Manual Edition Three, 1994 (Box 17)
  - Core Guidebook For New York State Child Protective Services Staff Trainers Manual Edition Four, 1995 (Box 17)
  - Legal References for Child Protective Service Workers, 1995 (Box 17)
  - Legal References for Child Protective Service Workers, 1996 (Box 17)
  - Legal References for Child Protective Service Workers, 1997 (Box 17)
  - Legal References for Child Protective Service Workers, 1998 (Box 17)
  - Legal References for Child Protective Service Workers, 1999 (Box 17)
  - Legal References for Child Protective Service Workers, 1999 (Box 17)
  - Core Guidebook For New York State Child Protective Services Staff Edition Four, 1996-03 (Box 17)
  - Trainer Manual For New York State Child Protective Services Workers Edition Four, 1995 (Box 18)
  - Core Training For New York State Child Protective Services Workers Supplement Edition One, 1995 (Box 18)
  - Supplemental CPS Core Training F or New York State Child Welfare Workers Edition One, 1995 (Box 18)
  - Supplemental CPS Core Training For New York State Child Welfare Workers Edition Two, 1996 (Box 18)
  - Supplemental CPS Core Training for New York State Child Welfare Workers Edition Three, 1996 (Box 18)
  - Supplemental CPS Core Training For New York State Child Welfare Workers Edition Four, 1996 (Box 18)
  - Child Protective Investigations Trainer Manual, 1998-12-10 (Box 18)
  - Core Guidebook For New York State Child Protective Services Staff Edition Five, 1999 (Box 18)
  - CPSTI Guidebook For New York State Child Protective Services Workers Edition Six, 2000 (Box 18)
  - Child Protective Investigations, 12/01/98 (Box 18)
  - Legal References for Child Protective Service Workers, 2000 (Box 18)
  - New York State Risk Assessment and Services Planning Model Bates Case Guidebook, 1992 (Box 19)
  - New York State Risk Assessment and Services Planning Model Bates Case Trainers Manual, 1992 (Box 19)
  - New York State Risk Assessment and Services Planning Model Field Guide, 1990-1991 (Box 19)
  - Bates Videos (Box 19)
  - New York State Risk Assessment and Services Planning Model Miller/Brown Guidebook (Box 19)
  - New York State Risk Assessment and Services Planning Model Field Guide, 1992 (Box 19)
  - Baker Video (Box 19)
  - Keesha Miller Video (Box 19)
  - New York State Risk Assessment and Services Planning Model Thompson Case Guidebook, 1992 (Box 19)
  - New York State Risk Assessment and Services Planning Model Thompson Case Trainers Manual, 1992 (Box 19)
  - New York State Risk Assessment and Services Planning Model Field Guide, 1992 (Box 19)
  - Andy Thompson Videos (Box 19)
  - Nancy Thompson Videos (Box 19)
  - New York State Risk Assessment and Services Planning Model Trainer Manual, 1993 (Box 19)
  - New York State Risk Assessment and Services Planning Model Field Guide, 1992 (Box 19)
  - Ruth the Source Videos (Box 19)
  - Evaluation report of the Basic training of the Child Protective Services Training Institute 1981 (Box 20)
  - Final Program Report, 1986-10-01-1988-03-31 (Box 20)
  - New York State Child Protective Services Training Institute- Child Protective Services Announcement of Programs, 1991-1992 (Box 20)
  - NYS Child Protective Services Training Institute - Residential Child Care Announcement of Programs, 1991-1992 (Box 20)
  - Final Program Report, 1991-07-01-1993-03-31 (Box 20)
  - Final Program Report, 1992-10-1994-03 (Box 20)
  - Annual Report, 1993-10-01-1994-09-30 (Box 20)
  - Report of findings CENSUS, 1995-02-08 (Box 20)
  - CENSUS Survey, 1995-02-08 (Box 20)
  - Quarterly Report, 1994-01-01-1994-03-31 (Box 20)
  - Quarterly Report, 1994-04-01-1994-06-30 (Box 20)
  - Quarterly Report, 1994-07-01-1994-09-30 (Box 20)
  - 1st Quarterly Report, 1994-10-01-1994-12-31 (Box 20)
  - Program Announcement, 1994-1995 (Box 20)
  - Trainee Rosters, 1994-1995 (Box 20)
  - 2nd Quarterly Report, 1995-01-01-1995-03-31 (Box 20)
  - 3rd Quarterly Report, 1995-04-01-1995-06-30 (Box 20)
  - 4th Quarterly Report, 1995-07-01-1995-09-30 (Box 20)
  - 1st Quarterly Report, 1995-10-01-1995-12-31 (Box 20)
  - Annual Report, 1994-10-01-1995-09-30 (Box 20)
  - Trainee Rosters, 1995 (Box 20)
  - INTERIM CPI materials, 2000 (Box 20)
  - Legal Issues Update Teleconferences (Box 20)
  - Video, 1998 (Box 20)
  - Video, 2000 (Box 20)
  - Video, 2001 (Box 20)
  - 1st Quarterly Report, 1996-10-01-1996-12-31 (Box 21)
  - 2nd Quarterly Report, 1996-01-01-1996-03-31 (Box 21)
  - 3rd Quarterly Report, 1996-04-01-1996-06-30 (Box 21)
  - 4th Quarterly Report, 1996-07-01-1996-09-30 (Box 21)
  - Annual Report, 1995-10-01-1996-09-30 (Box 21)
  - Program Announcement, 1995-1996 (Box 21)
  - Trainee Rosters, 1996 (Box 21)
  - 2nd Quarterly Report, 1997-01-01-1997-03-31 (Box 21)
  - 3rd Quarterly Report, 1997-04-01-1997-06-30 (Box 21)
  - 4th Quarterly Report, 1997-07-01-1997-09-30 (Box 21)
  - 1st Quarterly Report, 1997-10-01-1997-12-31 (Box 21)
  - Trainee Rosters, 1997 (Box 21)
  - Quarterly Report, 1998-01-01-1998-03-31 (Box 21)
  - 2nd Quarterly Report, 1998-04-01-1998-06-30 (Box 21)
  - 3rd Quarterly Report, 1998-07-01-1998-09-30 (Box 21)
  - 4th Quarterly Report (Revised), 1998-10-01-1998-12-31 (Box 21)
  - Trainee Rosters, 1998 (Box 21)
  - 1st Quarterly Report, 1999-01-01-1999-03-31 (Box 21)
  - 2nd Quarterly Report, 1999-04-01-1999-06-30 (Box 21)
  - 3rd Quarterly Report, 1999-07-01-1999-09-30 (Box 21)
  - 4th Quarterly Report, 1999-10-01-1999-12-31 (Box 21)
  - Trainee Rosters, 1999 (Box 21)
  - 1st Quarterly Report, 2000-01-01-2000-03-31 (Box 22)
  - 2nd Quarterly Report, 2000-04-01-2000-06-30 (Box 22)
  - 3rd Quarterly Report, 2000-07-01-2000-09-30 (Box 22)
  - 4th Quarterly Report, 2000-10-01-2000-12-31 (Box 22)
  - Trainee Rosters, 2000 (Box 22)
  - 1st Quarterly Report, 2001-01-01-2001-03-31 (Box 22)
  - 2nd Quarterly Report, 2001-04-01-2001-06-30 (Box 22)
  - 3rd Quarterly Report, 2001-07-01-2001-09-30 (Box 22)
  - 4th Quarterly Report, 2001-10-01-2001-12-31 (Box 22)
  - Review of the CPSTI, 1979-2001 (Box 22)
  - Trainee Rosters, 2001 (Box 22)
  - Child Protective Services Worker Training Institute (CPSTI) Participant List, 1980-2001 (Box 22)
  - Alphabetical Listing: (Box 22)
  - Abair, J.-Dunham, P. (Box 22)
  - Dunn, E. to Lifford A. (Box 22)
  - Lifford, A. to Russell, K. (Box 22)
  - Russell, K. to Zyla V. (Box 22)
  - Alphabetical Listing by County: (Box 22)
  - Albany county to Lewis county (Box 22)
  - Lewis county to Niagara county (Box 22)
  - Niagara county to Ontario county (Box 22)
  - Ontario county to Saratoga county (Box 22)
  - Saratoga county to Suffolk county (Box 22)
  - Suffolk county to Sullivan county (Box 22)
  - Sullivan county to Washington county (Box 22)
  - Washington county to Yates county (Box 22)
- Series III: Reports/Proposals/Subject Files
  - New York State Assembly Report on the Family Life Development Center, 1974-12 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Parents and Schools Partnership: Final Report, 1986-07-03 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Proposal from Cornell to Operate a Regional Resource Center on Abuse and Neglect in Region II (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 2nd Quarterly Report-Region II Child Abuse and Neglect Resource Center, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Annual Report, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Annual Report, 1991, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - FLDC Strategic Plan 2000-2005, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Five Year Plan (1979); Organizational Chart (1989); Budget (1997), 1979-1997 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Annual Reports
    - Barry, Frank, 1978-2000 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Dotterweich, Jutta, 2001-2002 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Endres, Thomas, 2002-2003 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Enroth, Cynthia, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Hamilton, Mary Agnes, 2002-2003 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Holden, Martha, 1995-2003 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Leidy, Brian D., 1995-2003 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - McPheron, MaryLu, 2002-2003 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Nunno, Michael, 1979-2003 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Powers, Jane, 1989-2003 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Smith, Elliott, 2002-2003 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Thomas, Margaret Gilboy, 1981-1985; 1996; 1998; 2002-2003 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Trapanick, Frances, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Wise, Gregory, 2001-2002 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Subject Files
      - Historical Information: Section I, 1974-1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Copyright Registration/Consent Forms (Life Histories Book) (Box 1, Folder 25)
      - FLDC Advisory Council Minutes, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - FLDC-Grant Application-Second Year Funding, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - "What Kids Can Tell Us" - Critical Assessment of Interview Strategies (1996); "Making Sense of Senseless Violence" Project (1997), 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Series IV: Reviews
  - Review Committee Packet, 1990-09-14 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Review Committee Packet, 1990-09-24 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Section I-Book I, 1974-1987 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Section II-Book I (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Section II-Book II (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Section II-Book II (Continued) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Section II-Book III (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Section II-Book IV (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Section II-Book V (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Section II-Book V (Continued) (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Section III-Book I (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Section III-Book II (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Section III-Book III (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Section III-Book IV (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Section III-Book V (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Section III-Book VI (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - FLDC Review,: Slide set, script, and slides pertaining to New York State's Child Protective Services Law, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - FLDC-Review Committee Material, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - FLDC-Review Committee Material, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - FLDC External Review, 2005-09-25-2005-09-27 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Dean's response to the FLDC External Review, 2006-04-10 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Series V: National Data Archive on Child Abuse and Neglect (NDACAN)
  - Newsletter-UPDATA, 1990-2009 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Handbook for Contributors, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - External Review, 2002-2005 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Administrative Data Conference Summary Report, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Summer Research Institute Photos, 1994-2011 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Quarterly Reports, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Quarterly Reports, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Quarterly Reports, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Quarterly Reports, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Quarterly Reports, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Quarterly Reports, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Final Reports, 1992-1995 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Final Reports, 1995-2000 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Final Reports, 2000-2005 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Final Reports, 2006-2010 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Biannual Reports, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Biannual Reports, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Biannual Reports, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Biannual Reports, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Biannual Reports, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Biannual Reports, 2006 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Biannual Reports, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Biannual Reports, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Biannual Reports, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Biannual Reports, 2010 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Grant Proposal, 1987-1988 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Grant Proposal, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Grant Proposal, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Grant Proposal, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Grant Proposal, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Grant Proposal, 2005 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Grant Proposal, 2010 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Current Holdings, 1998-02 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Third National Incidence Study of Child Abuse and Neglect - Special Research Meeting, 1997-03 (Box 25, Folder 34)
- Series VI: The Military Projects
  - A. Army Family Advocacy Program
  - Prevention Resource Manual, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 1-4)
  - Prevention Services for New Parents Implementation Guidelines, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Guidelines for Non-Commissioned Officers, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Materials Evaluation Final Report, 1995-12-01 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Foster Care Resource Manual, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Spouse Abuse Manual, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Prevention System Application Usser's Guide, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Domestic Violence Lesson Plan, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 11-12)
  - Managing Out of Home Child Sexual Abuse Cases Installation Handbook, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Commander's Desk Guide, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Spouse Abuse Victim Advocacy, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Child Abuse Manual, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Final Report on the Introduction of the Performance-based Management Approach to Program Design, 1998-01 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Materials Evaluation Final Report, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Commander's Guide, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Commander's Guide, 2008 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Supporting Fathers:Resources on Fatherhood Initiatives, Undated (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - B. Various Advocacy Programs
  - Army Community Service Volunteer Leader Handbook, Undated (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Family Advocay Program Installation Data Base and Annual Report Application Reference Manual, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Commander's Desk Guide for the Marine Corps, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Command Family Advocacy Handbook, 1997-01 (Box 27, Folder 2)